<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<THESIS>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Xinggang ZHANG, Dan DAI, Yan TANG. Statistical Voronoi Model for Monodisperse Disk Packings[J]. Journal of South China University of Technology(Natural Science Edition), 2023, 51(2): 122-130. https://zrb.bjb.scut.edu.cn/CN/10.12141/j.issn.1000-565X.220340
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Xinggang Zhang,Dan Dai.Exact solutions for Janssen effect of lattice disk packing. Powder Technology,2023,420:118380.https://doi.org/10.1016/j.powtec.2023.118380
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Chuang Zhao, Xinggang Zhang, Qingqing Gao, Chengbo Li.Discrete element simulation of particles defined by cardioids.Powder Technology,2022,404:117460.https://doi.org/10.1016/j.powtec.2022.117460
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            ZHANG Xinggang,CAO Lei.Similarity diagonalization of a tridiagonal matrix and its applications.Journal of Guizhou University(Natural Sciences),2021，38（6）：19-24.DOI：10.15958/j.cnki.gdxbzrb.2021.06.03
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Xinggang Zhang,Dan Dai.Aspects of bulk properties of amorphous jammed disks under isotropic compression. Eur. Phys. J. E，2021，44（11）：140(1-11). https://doi.org/10.1140/epje/s10189-021-00145-3
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Xinggang Zhang,Dan Dai.Exact solutions for stress distribution in rhombic disk packings. Granular Matter，2021，23(2):1-9. https://doi.org/10.1007/s10035-021-01120-7
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Xinggang Zhang,Dan Dai.Governing equations for stress distribution in rhombic disk packings.Physica A: Statistical Mechanics and its Applications,2020,558(15):124911. https://doi.org/10.1016/j.physa.2020.124911
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Dai Dan，Zhang Xinggang.Periodic noise elimination algorithm based on morphological filtering with auto-adapted weights.Computer Technology and Development,2017,(5):.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            ZHOU Hua，LEI Xian-huan，TANG Shu-pan，ZAHNG Duo，ZHANG Xing-gang.Particle Image Processing in Granular Stress Test[J]. Modern Computer,2017,32 : 71-75.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Dai Dan.Exploration of teaching contents of linear algebra for physics majors[J]. Journal of Science of Teachers′College and University,2017,37( 5) : 70-73.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin.Basic properties of two-dimensional soft sphere system under isotropic compression[J]. Chinese J Comput. Phys,2017,34( 2) : 245-252.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Dai Dan. Lattice model for pressure problems in two-dimensional granular columns [J]. Acta Physica Sinica,2017, 66(20), 204501.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Wei,Hu Lin,Zhang Xinggang. Structural features of critical jammed state in bi-disperse granular systems[J].Acta Physica Sinica,2016, 65(2):217-222.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Yang Lin,Hu Lin, Zhang Xinggang. Lateral pressure distribution and steering coeﬃcient in two-dimensional lattice pile of granular material[J].Acta Physica Sinica,2015, 64(13):220-226.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Yang Lin,Hu Lin, Zhang Xinggang.The Influence of boundary friction factors on geometry of two-dimensional granular systems[J]. Journal of Shandong University,2015,50(9):7-12.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin.Effect of friction on the critical jammed states of two-dimensional granular systems[J]. Journal of Shandong University,2015,50(3):40-44.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin. Compression of jammed states of two-dimensional frictionless particles[J]. Chinese J Comput. Phys,2015,32( 2) : 247-252.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin. The application of Dirac function in ensemble theory[J]. Journal of Guizhou University,2014,31( 6) : 20-24.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            GAO Li-ke，HU Lin ，ZHANG Xing-gang，DENG Xiong.Experimental investigation on the relationship between steering coefficient and volume fraction in two-dimensional static granular system[J]. Journal of Shandong University,2015,49(1):54-58.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin. Tangential force distribution in granular system of compositional disorder[J]．Chinese J Comput. Phys,2012,29( 4) : 627-632.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin. Normal force distribution in two-dimensional granular system of compositional disorder[J]. Acta Physica Sinica,2012, 61(10), 244-251.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang, Hu Lin. The Integral of Probability Density Function in Force Network Ensemble[J].Journal of Shandong University,2011,46(7):35-42.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Kong Weishu,Hu Lin,Zhang Xinggang. Experimental study on relation between volume fraction of sandpiles and flow rate of forming sandpiles[J].Acta Physica Sinica,2010, 59(1):411-416.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang,Long Zhengwen, Hu Lin.The Scalar Force Network Ensemble Model for Force Distribution in Granular System[J].Acta Physica Sinica,2009, 58(1):90-96
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang,Kong Weishu.Theoretical and Numerical Investigation of Elastic String with Fixed Ends[J]. Journal of Shandong University,2008,43(10):1-6.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Kong Wei Shu,Hu Lin,Du Xue Neng,Zhang Xing Gang.Studies of maximum static friction force in granular pile with probing rod[J].Acta Physica Sinica,2007, 58(4):2318-2322.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
    <thesis>
        <detaile>
            Zhang Xinggang,Long Zhengwen, Hu Lin.A Model of Disc Pile with Silo Effect[J]．Chinese J Comput. Phys,2006,23( 6) : 642-646.
        </detaile>
    </thesis>
</THESIS>